# SAWANT ADITYA RAVINDRA ARATI

Front End Developer addisawant1001@gmail.com +91 9820365585

Room no: 19, 61/c wani chawl, new prabhadevi road, near samna press, prabhadevi, Mumbai: 400025

10 Nov 1996

### About Me

I believe working in a challenging Environment with creative aspects that will help me to future my developer skills and help me to grow into a professional Developer. Motivated, teamwork-oriented, and responsible Web Developer with significant experience in web development with Well educated, perceived B.E. and certification in web-developer.

### Technical Skills

### REAT JS

Having good working knowledge of software development on several projects using react js framework. Develop and execute unit, functional, integration testing of developed software components.

#### **J-QUERY**

Good hands on implementing javascript library like j-query, able to create reusable code with such libraries.

#### **JAVASCRIPT**

Understanding of object-oriented-programming language, reusable Javascript. Experience with usage and implementation of javascript framework.

### CSS<sub>3</sub>

Good working knowledge of generating responsive designs for desktop as well as mobile view with the help of CSS 3 style sheet, also having great hands on SCSS tool for more suitable format.

### HTML 5

Having best hands on creating web structure on HTML5 mark-up language, strong working knowledge on following html standard structure and use of preferable html tag.

### Education

### **Front End Development Course**

Net-Tech Network Training Institute (2019)
I have completed my Front End Developing Cource with the respective institute

### **B.E.** (Bachelor of Engineering)

Viva Institute of Technology, Virar (2015 - 2018)
I have pursuit my B.E. with first class from the respective institute

### **Diploma in Engineering**

Government Polytechnic, Mumbai (2012 - 2015)

I have pursuit my Diploma with first class from the respective institute

### S.S.C.

Maharashtra State Board (2011 - 2012)

## Work Experience

### PRDXN, React Front End Developer

(From Jan2020 - Present)

#### PRESENTATION MAKER APP

- Work closely with react js framework business and multiple development, architecture, design, and test teams to implement next generation application.
- Design and Write code for web/mobile HTML 5 service-driven applications that scale to high-volume production instances, which includes test-driven and quality centric solutions.
- The Main Moto of this app to take inputs from user and make presentation PPTX file based on different inputs added by user.
- The App is basically divided in two core sections where one is Admin side panel and another user side panel, where admin having all the access of app, and he can manage the users access.
- Work experience with **git** branching structure, and resolving conflicts.
- Had great working experience with react is framework while building this project.
- had experience of Deployment of app using AWS environment.

#### LANDING PAGE MAKER TOOL

- The main moto of this tool is to generate landing page which consist of html and css zip file.
- It is the sub-sequent tool present in Presentation Maker App, user can make landing page for it's own projects.
- Deliver quality code by applying the best development practices.

### REMI ELECTROMAGNETIC, Supervisor

(From Jan2019 - Dec2019)

#### PRESS SHOP DEPARTMENT

- Accomplishes department objectives by supervising staff and organizing and monitoring work process.
- Maintains safe and healthy work environment by establishing and enforcing organization standards and adhering to legal regulations.

# Certification

### Front End Developer Certification

From Net-tech Network Training institute

### Web Developer Certification

From PRDXN for successfully completing training of web development

# Personal Information

### **Git-Hub link**

https://github.com/sadityacode

### **Languages Known**

Marathi, Hindi, English

#### **Personal Skills**

- Sociability
- Punctuality
- Creativity

#### Hobbies

Sketching , Designing, Sports, Music